carethy.net 2018-07-18

# Privacy policy - Carethy

**General Regulation of Data Protection (RGDP) - May 2018.**

We inform you that the personal details of our Customers will be treated in accordance with the principles of transparency, purpose limitation, data minimisation, accuracy, integrity and confidentiality, as well as respecting the rest of the obligations and guarantees established in the (EU) Regulation 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of the 27th April 2016 relative to the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and the free movement of such data.

In order to comply with the above Regulation, we have updated our Privacy Policy:

  * **Responsible:**   Carethy E-commerce S.L, Tax ID Number: B67129486, address: C/ De la Física, Num. 2-4 A7 Llinars Park, 08450 Llinars Del Valles - (Barcelona), Telephone: 0034 93 396 71 72, email: support@carethy.net
  * **Purpose of processing** : we use the information you provide us to be able to provide you the service you requested, send you communications concerning the purchased products or similar products, and to invoice for them.
  * **Origin and category of processed data** : the personal data we use are your identification details that you provide us with using the registration form that you will find on our Website.
  * **Conservation period** : the data provided will be stored as long as you maintain a business relationship with us or for the required number of years to be able to comply with legal obligations.
  * **Legitimacy** : we only process your data with your express consent to do so, and always in accordance with the described purposes.
  * **Recipients** : the data that you provide to us will not be disclosed to third parties except in cases where there is a legal obligation to do so.

In order to carry out certain necessary functions to provide the service, your data may be processed by third parties who act as data processors and who are contractually obliged to comply with the legal obligations of data processing, to keep information secret and confidential.

**International Transfers** : we inform you that the Company contracts the management of some functions required to provide the service to data processors situated outside of the EU and that they guarantee a suitable level of protection of personal data.

  * **Rights** : you are the owner of the following rights regarding your personal data:
  * Right to request access to personal data.
  * Right to request rectification or erasure.
  * Right to request restriction or opposition to data processing.
  * Right to data portability.
  * Revocation of the consent given.

To exercise these rights you must send us written notification by email to the following address: [support@carethy.net](mailto:support@carethy.net)  specifying the right you wish to exercise.

Furthermore, we inform you that you may request the protection of your rights from the Spanish Data Protection Agency with its headquarters in Calle de Jorge Juan, 6, 28001 Madrid.

**COOKIES**

Terms of web browser cookies. Corporate Section. (UPDATE PRIVACY PAGE WITH THE NEW COOKIES CONTENT). Web Browser Cookies Policy. Please be advised that our site uses cookies to track and analyse User visits. We utilize this information to best determine our customer needs and hence it enables us to offer a more refined and enhanced service. When browsing our website, User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for the reasons stated above in addition to record-keeping purposes. Each and every application for tracking cookies has been developed by statistics companies and under no circumstance track or relate to User's name or e-mail address. The information gathered is related with, for example, the product types visited, categories browsed, the browsing language, time spent on inspecting products, the total number of visitors or the type of web browser used. User may permit, find information on, disable or delete cookies by using User's web browser's configuration tools. For more information on the matter, User should consult the following links depending on the browser used:

Mozilla Firefox: [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/search?q=cookies&esab=a](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/search?q=cookies&esab=a)[](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/search?q=cookies&esab=a)

Google Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>[](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)

Internet Explorer: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10>[](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10)

Apple Safari: [http://support.apple.com/kb/index?page=search&src=support_site.kbase.search&q=cookies&locale=en_US](http://support.apple.com/kb/index?page=search&src=support_site.kbase.search&q=cookies&locale=en_US)[](http://support.apple.com/kb/index?page=search&src=support_site.kbase.search&q=cookies&locale=en_US)

Opera Browser: <http://help.opera.com/Linux/10.10/en/cookies.html>

This site uses our own and third pary owned cookies, in order to give you a personalized service. If you continue to navigate on our site, we consider you accept their use. Either way, you can change the settings on your browser. For more information, please refer to our [privacy policy](https://www.carethy.net/corp/privacy-policy).
